Fried, Philoine Additional Files and Memorabilia 6064
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Philoine Fried Additional Files and Memorabilia
1946-2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Fried, Philoine
6064
7.78 cubic feet
2.1 linear ft.
Papers, photographs, news clippings, publications, speeches, memmorabilia.
5791187
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 09, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 28, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6015 P: ACWA Hyman Blumberg Photographs
5791187
- 15th Biennial Convention 1946 Atlantic City, N.J. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Photographs, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  3 Photographs
- FDR and Truman, Correspondence 1938-1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Clipping (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Invitations Paris 1945 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Newspapers + Credit Cards 1946 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Hillman, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Paper (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Handwritten in Russian
- Clippings, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Newspapers + Bulletins, 1946-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Booklets (America), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  1 booklet in Hindi
- Time Magazine & Labor and Nation 1946 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bessie Conference, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Current Biography, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Speeches - Hillman (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Czecho Labor Policy, 1937-1940 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Bessie Hillman - Papers, Letters, 1966-1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1932-1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- General Marshall's Report & 'Look' Magazine, 1943-1950 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Delegates Badges, 1955-1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  3 small boxes of badges
- Photographs, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Condolence Cards to Philoine Fried on Father's Death, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bessie Hillman's Get-well cards, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Bessie Hillman's Christmas Cards, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Jeff, Joanna, and Michael letters, 1972-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Sidney Hillman, 1981-1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Address books and cards (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Miami Fed. 2005- (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Hillman, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Sidney Hillman Documents, 1945-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- New Jewish Politics for an American Labor Leader, 1942-1946 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Sidney Hillman -, 1992-2004 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Passports, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- German Memorabilia, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Correspondence + Invitations, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Banks Books (Box 2, Folder 17)
- News Clippings, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Broadside (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Sidney Hillman Speeches (Box 3, Folder 1)